Now that you've learned to use Git to control the version
of both your local and remote repositories,
it's time to put your skills to work.
In this project, you will simulate the workflow used in
industry on the bike share code you completed for the previous project.
Now, there will be four main parts to this project.
First, you'll set up your repository on both your local machine and then up on GitHub.
Then, you'll improve the documentation on a documentation branch.
Third, you'll refactor your code on a refactoring branch.
The actual part of your code that you choose to refactor for this doesn't really matter.
Finally, you'll need to merge all of your branches
together and add the changes to the remote repository.
The following pages will lead you through this process and inform
you about what the guidelines are for submission. Good luck.